# **AXLE RODRIGUEZ**

Marikina Height, Marikina City

0906-2433-195

rodriguez.imaxle@gmail.com

https://axle21.github.io

### ° SKILLS °

#### **Programming Languages**

- HTML5
- CSS (Sass)
- PHP (Slim , Codeigniter)
- JavaScript (ReactJS, VanillaJS)
- C++

#### **Content Management System**

- WordPress
- Adobe Experience Manager

#### **Database Management**

- Maria DB
- SQL Server
- Oracle
- Postgre
- MySQL

### **Reporting Tool**

- Crystal Report
- Eclipse Birt Report

# **Versioning Tool**

 Git version- control system

## **Graphic Design Tools**

- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- After Effect
- Power Director

# PROFILE

Dedicated on Web Development with around 5 years' experience creating and maintaining functional, attractive, and responsive websites. Clear understanding of modern technologies and best design practices. Have a strong creative and analytical skills that can work as a team player, as well as independently with minimal supervision.

# **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

Tech Support / Programmer at 8Box Solutions Inc.

March – September 2015

- Developing CRM application using PHP that will fit to clients need.
- Creating Report for the CRM application.

#### Jr. Programmer at Accent Micro Technology Inc.

March 2016 - May 2017

- Focus on developing in house web application for the company's need using PHP (Codeigniter) as MVC framework and eclipse Birt report for reporting tool.
- Creating / querying data from Oracle database upon user request.

# Web Developer at Concentrix

May 2017 - March 2019

- Develop EDM that follows the best practices for email.
- Work with ADOBE Experience Manager as needed for maintaining and developing client's sites.

### PHP Developer at People Partners BPO Inc.

June 2019 - January 2020

- Web Development / Maintenance of client site using WordPress.
- Developing school base web application that will replace the current one that being used by the company, using React.js as frontend and PHP (Slim) as backend.
- Working with Rest API Web Services.

## **EDUCATION**

### **B.S INFORMATION AND TECHNOLOGY**

ABE International Business College

Aurora Blvd Cubao QC. / 2015